[Music]
It starts with a simple but powerful
mission for clean sport. Champion
athletes to achieve their dreams in a
fair and healthy way and to inspire the
world. Guided by this mission, we stand
with athletes and for athletes from the
start of their careers to the day they
retire. When they first enter sport, we
are there to help them learn the lessons
and values needed for success on and off
the field. As they ascend to higher
levels of sport, we are there with
education and resources that help them
navigate the anti-doping process. When
their success makes them eligible for
testing, we are there with a friendly
face and consistent protocols to guide
them through the process. When they have
a question about substances and methods,
we have experts available a phone call
away and at the forefront of the effort
to solve the most complex anti-doping
questions. If they run into issues with
the rules, we're there with a fair
adjudication process that protects the
rights of all athletes as well as a
steadfast voice to advocate for
improvements to the global anti-doping
system. And when the day comes for them
to start a new journey, we're there to
process their retirement and celebrate
their commitment to clean
sport. From the first whistle to the
final buzzer, USADA is championing
athletes to achieve their dreams in a
fair and healthy way so they can inspire
the world.